[Music]
Mommy
I have been adding honey and grapefruit
to my green tea every morning lately and
I have to admit it is just delicious I
only have caffeinated drinks about once
a week or so but today this green tea
was much needed because because I have
to admit to you I'm very
tired I am so tired and I don't really
know why I cannot come up with an
explanation only that I am I had plans
to go skiing and go on a big hike and
Adventure through a certain part of the
forest I haven't gone to yet and all of
those plans are disintegrating before my
eyes however my spirits are still quite
High because I have an extremely
exciting project today and it has to do
with books and bookshelves Luke has been
kind enough to make me some new
bookshelves and they are a great
Improvement on the ones I had which
while they look lovely are quite rickety
so I am so happy about it and I'm very
excited to be reorganizing and
decorating my books and hopefully
dividing them up to find which ones I
should give away because let's be honest
I have too many books I've said in past
videos that there's no such thing as too
many books but in my case starting this
new year because I no longer work at my
bookstore I taking a break for now to
try to figure out some other things with
my schedule I am going to be using the
library a lot so I want to minimize my
selection give some away give some to
friends but of course that's going to be
very hard to do because they're my books
they are your non-sentient children so
it will not be easy but I am excited
because what better way to spend the
evening for a book lover than organizing
a bookshelf
[Music]
so these are the bookshelves that Luke
made me when he asked me what my vision
was I just said that I wanted to feel
like I had a little library in a fairy
home in the forest and so he made these
raw wood edged bookshelves and I just
think they're so unique and beautiful
and they smell delicious too so I
couldn't be happier and I feel like it
is going to to look just magical once I
load them
[Music]
so after much deliberation I think these
are the books I'm going to go through
and decide which ones I'm going to re
home and donate I have a lot of people
in my life who love to read I worked at
as a book seller for years and went to
little thrift shops often to get books
so I think probably the average price of
any of these books is a matter of sents
or they were just free so it has been
very easy to collect books over the
years due to that so I think it is high
time though that I gave some of them
away to people who also love to read so
I think these are the books I'm going to
keep it was uh quite difficult to make
that decision
but at least I downsized quite a bit so
it is a good start I think it is now
time though to load them onto the
bookshelf which is really exciting
[Music]
ma'am what are you doing
huh for
[Music]
I had just the most wonderful time doing
this it has been raining outside and so
I wasn't really planning to be outdoors
it's super icy and slippery so this was
the perfect entertainment I'm so
grateful for my husband because he found
these pieces of wood at affordable
prices or just for free because it was
scrap wood or recycled wood and he put
so much time and effort into this and I
just think it's so unique and so
beautiful I'm going to go ahead and do a
bit of a bookshelf tour I am not going
to go through every single book but I
thought I would point out my favorites
within each section I'm not necessarily
going to recommend all the books on my
shelf there are of course mixed in ones
that I have not read and cannot give you
an opinion on so I will stick to the
ones I know and then I will share with
you some of the books that were very
important to me throughout my life
growing up at the top left of my
bookshelf there are all my cozy
Mysteries they are definitely guilty
pleasures then we go on to mostly
fantasy and fiction mixed together a lot
of them are Advanced reader copies or
copies I got at
[Music]
discount then there is my section for
reference and more spiritual books as
well as non-fiction
then on the third shelf are all my
Classics and much older books that I've
gotten at thrift stores usually for just
a couple dollars and then of course
there is more
fiction I have a section just for
graphic novels I love seeing art and
writing put together in this way as well
as a lot of other series and other
collections of books most of which I've
had since I was very very young I grew
up in a family of big readers and my
parents were always encouraging me by
taking me to the library and getting me
books for my
birthday and at the very bottom there
are reference books as well as
collections of short stories as well as
all my childhood books many which are
very battered and worn this month I got
my hands on an advanced copy of the moth
keeper which I really loved I also read
this cute little book called garlic and
the witch if you are an English major I
think you might like the book jumper it
is such a fun adventure I also love the
book Kenny and the Dragon it is just an
adorable adventure story I also recently
discovered this children's book
Heartwood hotel which is just so cute
and
innocent so I wanted to take a moment to
just go through some books that were
very influential and meaningful to me
growing up and have had a part to play
in who I am today and so I will add the
disclaimer that these are not impressive
books these are not some self-help books
or highly academic or intellectual books
at all these are mostly children's books
however I believe that the books we read
as children and the books we love as
children influence us greatly in ways
that we could never measure particularly
as we become adults and that is
certainly the truth for myself and one
of the reasons I believe that is that
when I worked at a bookstore I would ask
people what they were reading recently
and they would have a hard time coming
up with some book recommendations but if
I asked them the books that they loved
as children they could always give me at
least two or three titles of books they
were obsessed with and it's something
that really sticks with them and stays
with them and I think that's really
beautiful I am no different so I will
begin with this battered copy of the
girls book of flower fairies it was
certainly one of um the most important
books for me especially as an artist
because I would page through it again
and again and again and it has water
damage it has gone through all the
elements it is just about falling apart
but it is so special to me because it
really helped me get inspired to start
painting fairies and creating fairy art
which is now one of the types of art
that I create for my Etsy Shop the same
goes for betri Potter's collection of
Peter Rabbit stories and Beyond and they
really influenced my art as well and
speaking of thank you so much for the
support of my Etsy Shop it really helps
keep everything over here happening with
my channel and with my Art thank you
other books that influenced my
imagination and love of reading were the
red wall books by Brian
Jake the Apothecary by m miloy i I feel
like I'm butchering that name but I love
this series growing up as well I also
absolutely loved the penderwick and the
evolution of caleria Tate I read so many
books about young girls figuring out how
to be their best selves and find their
confidence and I think that was really
important for me when I was very young
sometimes all you need is a hero or
heroine to look up to that really
inspires you to really make that extra
step to you know kind of become someone
you want to be last but not least there
is Arthur spiderwick's Field Guide which
is a field guide based upon the book
series of the Spiderwick Chronicles
which I was obsessed with as a child and
I think this field guide was extremely
special to me growing up because it got
me outside in the forest looking for
fairies I was an enormous believer and I
was taking this book out with me along
with binoculars and magnifying glasses
and I was dedicated to finding some of
these creatures and I even remember I
wrote to the author of the books Holly
black and I asked her for some advice
for finding fairies and she gave me
detailed advice in her letter on how to
do it it was so sweet and it definitely
fed my passion I have a lot of classic
books you know for adults and things
like that that I've read that have
impacted me greatly but when I was
thinking of the books that have had the
greatest impact on me I really can only
think of childhood books because as an
adult I think you are a little more
critical and maybe books do not have the
same wait as often as when you are a
child and so that's why I wanted to
mention those but for books for adults
that I love and recommend I've made
countless videos on them so I will leave
links down below if you would like more
book recommendations I hope you have a
wonderful week thank you so much for
being here and for sharing your lovely
comments down below and I will see you
very soon goodbye
[Music]